Lynes, George Platt, 1907-1955. George Lynes Platt photographs, 1935-1953 (MS Thr 483): Guide.
George Lynes Platt photographs,
- Kokoschka, Oskar, 1886-., (Box 2)
  His right hand resting on top of his left hand, both hands on top of fan, looking right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,782.
  Number on photograph: 105-7.
- Kokoschka, Oskar, 1886-., (Box 2)
  His left elbow resting on fan with his left index finger pointed up, his right hand on hip, looking forward and slightly up.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,783.
  Number on photograph: 105-5.
- Kokoschka, Oskar, 1886-., (Box 2)
  Standing, his left hand resting on stool, his right hand in his pocket, looking forward.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,784.
  Number on photograph: 105-10.
- Lancaster, Burt., (Box 2)
  Waist-up shot; seated on chair, looking right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,688.
- Lancaster, Burt., (Box 2)
  Seated in room with open window and a painting, legs propped on a table, someone else's legs mingling with his on tabletop (second person's face and body not visible).
  HTC No.: HTC 20,689.
- Lancaster, Burt., (Box 2)
  Seated in room with closed window and a painting, angled in chair to look at painting.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,690.
- Lifar, Serge., (Box 2)
  In Indian costume, wearing ornate headdress, seated in front of greenery, body facing left; eyes shut, his right thumb at lips.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,868.
  Number on photograph: 191 A.
- Lifar, Serge., (Box 2)
  In ruffled leotard and slippers, seated with left leg bent under. Right leg outstretched, leaning on left arm with right arm bent and raised.
- Lynes, Akin., (Box 2)
  Leaning with her elbows on the back of a bench, looking at a flower in her right hand.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,785.
- Lynes, Elizabeth., (Box 3)
  Nude, standing facing back, looking left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,786.
- Lynes, Elizabeth., (Box 3)
  Nude, lying on her stomach on platform covered with a painter's drip cloth.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,787.
- Lynes, Elizabeth., (Box 3)
  Nude, lying on her back on a raised platform covered with a painter's drip cloth.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,788.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  In fur-lined coat with hand on bookshelf, facing right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,640.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Seated, staring at floor.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,641.
  Number on photograph: Eastman-Safety-Kodak 110.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Camera hoisted over head, both arms raised in circular shape.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,642.
  Number on photograph: 378-15; Kodak Safety 87.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Camera hoisted over head, his left arm higher than his right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,643.
  Number on photograph: 378-19; Kodak Safety 87.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Standing beside camera.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,644.
  Number on photograph: 378-14; Kodak Safety 87.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Camera above head, his left hand on trigger and his right hand resting on a piece of wood.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,645.
  Number on photograph: 378-21; Kodak Safety 87.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Camera at shoulder level, his right arm propped on the box, circular lights on left side of proof.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,646.
  Number on photograph: 378-3; Kodak Safety 87.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Camera at shoulder level, his left hand on the trigger, circular lights on left side of proof.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,647.
  Number on photograph: 378-6; Kodak Safety 87.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Camera at shoulder level, his left hand resting on the box, collar turned up; same proof as HTC 20,649 with slightly lighter exposure.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,648.
  Number on photograph: 378-8; Kodak Safety 87.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Camera at shoulder level, his left hand resting on the box, collar turned up; same proof as HTC 20,648 with slightly darker exposure.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,649.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Camera above head, his right hand raised, looking down and to our right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,650.
  Number on photograph: 378-11; Kodak Safety 87.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Camera above head, his left hand on trigger and his right hand with fingers spread wide on a piece of wood; of his face only eyes and the bridge of his nose are visible.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,651.
  Number on photograph: 378-22; Kodak Safety 87.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Contact sheet; various poses shirtless on large bed; second proof up from bottom in far right column is marked to be cut; back reads "80.00 60.94" and "je ne coucoir avenue superiorite, que la bonte #."
  HTC No.: HTC 20,694.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Wearing button-up khaki shirt with the sleeves rolled up, his left hand at waist, his right hand holding a cigarette to his mouth, head tilted slightly left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,789.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Wearing button-up khaki shirt with the sleeves rolled up, his hands at sides, looking forward.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,790.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Seated on back of chair, legs spread, elbows resting on knees, looking left; wearing dress shirt, tie, and dark pants; cigarette in his left hand; hands clasped; large ring on his left hand.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,791.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Seated on floor in family-room-type area, legs crossed, baby in lap, both Lynes and baby sitting straight up and looking at camera.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,792.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Seated on floor in family-room-type area, legs crossed, baby in lap; baby crawling over Lynes' right knee and looking at camera, Lynes leaning to left and smiling at baby.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,793.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Seated on couch in living room, wearing suit and tie, looking slightly left, smiling.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,794.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Seated on couch in living room, wearing suit and tie, looking slightly left, not smiling.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,795.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Camera looking up at Lynes from knee-level at a steep angle; Lynes standing in front of ornate building (church?) and looking left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,796.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Lynes in white bathing trunks ar beach, standing in front of a sand dune, hands at sides, looking right and squinting.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,797.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Lynes and another man sitting back-to back on a rock; behind them, what looks like a Southwestern church.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,798.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 3)
  Sunset at the beach; a man and a woman holding a sheet behind Lynes, who, shirtless, is raising his arms and looking up towards the sky.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,799.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 2)
  Lynes and another man at the beach; Lynes seated and looking to his left, smiling at a small dog; the other man standing with his hands on Lynes' shoulders, smiling at camera.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,800.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 2)
  Undersized photograph (approximately 4-3/4" by 6-1/2"); Lynes and a nother man in a garden; other man crouching down amidst plants, Lynes standing behind him with hands on hips.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,801.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 2)
  Lynes and another man at the beach; Lynes seated and looking to his left, smiling at a small dog; the other man seated to the left of Lynes, petting the dog.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,802.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 2)
  View of Lynes from the shoulders up lying in a bed of leaves and cradling a small dog.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,803.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 2)
  Lynes standing in front of a tree and slightly behind a stone urn with vines, his left profile from the waist up contained mostly in the bottom right quadrant of the photo.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,804.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 2)
  Sitting on couch in living room, looking out window to the left; holding a cigarette in his right hand and a pair of glasses in his left hand.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,805.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 2)
  Seated, elbows on knees, left profile, shirtless, outdoors, people in background.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,806.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 2)
  Seated, elbows on knees, left profile, shirtless, outdoors, people in background; identical to HTC 20,806 except for damage spots in the center of photo.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,807.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 2)
  Standing on porch with woman, leaning against column and facing right (towards building), woman leaning against the column behind him and also facing right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,808.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 2)
  Young Lynes wearing denim jacket, viewed from the waist up, eyes cast down to bottom left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,809.
- Lynes, George Platt., (Box 2)
  Seated in bare room (appears to be studio or basement), wearing dress coat, vest, and tie, his right hand clasping his left wrist, looking left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,882.
  Number on photograph: 816 A.
- Lynes, George Platt, 1935., (Box 3)
  View from the shoulders up, leaning against brick wall, his right arm raised above his head, looking up, face mostly obscured.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,883.
  Number on photograph: 358 A.
- Lynes, George Platt, 1932., (Box 3)
  Lynes seen through two torn canvas screens; standing, arms crossed, with cigarette in his right hand.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,902.
- Lynes, George Platt, 1928., (Box 3)
  Viewed from shoulders up, his right shoulder and face facing the camera, looking behind him (to the left); black background; undersized photograph (approx. 7.5" by 9").
  HTC No.: HTC 20,937.
- Lynes, George Platt; with others., (Box 3)
  Contact sheet: 16 proofs taken at the beach.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,614.
- Lynes, George Platt, (Box 3)
  In Harlequin tights (full length) with right arms raised, hand behind head, left arm raised with hand on forehead, large ring worn palm-side.
  HTC No.: HTC 22,651.
- Lynes, J. R., Jr.., (Box 3)
  Stroking dog.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,623.
  Number on photograph: Negative No. 239 A.
- Lynes, Russell., (Box 3)
  Lying in a pile of leaves with rake, facing forward.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,811.
- Lynes, Russell., (Box 3)
  Sitting at desk, eyeglasses in his right hand, arms on desk, looking right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,873.
- Lynes, Russell., (Box 3)
  Sitting at desk, eyeglasses in his right hand, arms on desk, looking left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,874.
- Lynes, Russell., (Box 3)
  Sitting at desk, wearing eyeglasses; Lynes' figure contained in bottom left quandrant of photo.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,875.
- Lynes, Russell., (Box 3)
  Standing with hands in pockets, facing front and looking right; figure contained in left half of photo.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,876.
- Magallanes, Nicky., (Box 3)
  Head shot; back reads "Nicholas Magallanes."
  HTC No.: HTC 20,622.
- Maisze, Mai., (Box 3)
  Seated on ladder, her arms wrapped around it, looking right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,813.
- Male Nude, 1947., (Box 5)
  Unidentified male nude in George Platt Lynes' bedroom; man is mostly hidden behind bed, only his arms and head visible as they are resting on the bed, hands clasped; bedside lamp turned on directly above figure.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,881.
  Location: Box 5 of 5.
- Mann, Thomas., (Box 4)
  Leaning against palm tree, facing forward, arms crossed, facing forward, looking forward.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,814.
- Mann, Thomas., (Box 4)
  Leaning against palm tree, hat in hand, facing left, looking slightly forward, small smile.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,815.
- Mann, Thomas., (Box 4)
  Leaning against palm tree, hat in hand, facing left, looking full forward, lip spursed.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,816.
- Mann, Thomas., (Box 4)
  Seated on bench by pond next to olarge black dog; looking left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,817.
- Markova, Alicia., (Box 4)
  Arabesque with driftwood sculpture.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,606.
  Number on photograph: 110.
- Maugham, Somerset., (Box 4)
  In suit, facing shirtless man.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,624.
  Number on photograph: 296-1.
- McCarthy, Buddy., (Box 4)
  Man in white undershirt seated in front of shadowed blinds.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,812.
- McClendon, Carlos., (Box 4)
  Lying on carpet, only head visible; crease down center.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,637.
  Number on photograph: 91.
- McClendon, Carlos, 1947., (Box 4)
  Seated on bed, wearing all white, looking right; back reads "H.S. H.R.J."
  HTC No.: HTC 20,818.
- McWilliam, Ralph, 1952., (Box 4)
  Twice-exposed photograph of dancer, facing front.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,619.
- McWilliam, Ralph, 1952., (Box 4)
  Twice-exposed photograph of dancer, facing back.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,621.
- Miller, Bill, 1945., (Box 4)
  Dance study; silver print; weight on his right leg, his left toe pointed, his left hand touching his left thigh, looking right; back of proof marked with the letter F.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,696.
- Miller, Bill, 1945., (Box 4)
  Dance study; silver print; both arms spread straight, looking left; back of proof marked with the letter F.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,697.
- Miller, Bill, 1945., (Box 4)
  Dance study; silver print; both arms raised and bent, looking right; back of proof marked with the letter F.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,698.
- Miller, Bill, 1950., (Box 4)
  Seated with his right leg bent, wearing bathrobe, looking left; silver print.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,705.
- Miller, Bill, 1950., (Box 4)
  Seated, wearing bathrobe around shoulders, frontally nude, looking right; silver print;.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,706.
- Miller, Bill, 1950., (Box 4)
  Seated, wearing bathrobe, facing front with hands on hips; silver print.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,707.
- Miller, Bill (?)., (Box 4)
  Seated, arms crossed across chest, not wearing pants.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,713.
- Miro, Joan, 1947., (Box 4)
  Undersized photograph (approx. 7 1/4" by 7 3/4"); holding frame containing a painting on fabric, standing in front of a mural, facing front.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,960.
- Model (Arthur Lee's model with shadow of Robert Bishop), 1938., (Box 4)
  Nude woman standing with her leg in torn canvas screen, shadow of Robert Bishop visible on wall behind her.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,916.
- Montgomery, George., (Box 4)
  Seated, clasping knees, looking forward.
  HTC No.: HTC 22,666.
- Montgomery, George., (Box 4)
  Seated, clasping knees, looking right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,819.
- Montgomery, George, 1950., (Box 4)
  Reclining on couch, viewed from shoulders up, left third of face obscured by pillow.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,936.
- Moore, Marianne., (Box 4)
  Young, seated, with fingers on cheek.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,625.
  Number on photograph: 713 A.
- Moore, Marianne., (Box 4)
  Seated, with blurred botanical background, facing front.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,626.
  Number on photograph: 150-6; 195-6.
- Moore, Marianne., (Box 4)
  Seated, facing right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,627.
  Number on photograph: 150-22; 195-22.
- Moore, Marianne., (Box 4)
  Seated, with gray background, chin slightly raised; number 150-19 is scratched out at top of proof.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,628.
  Number on photograph: 195-19; Kodak Safety 47.
- Moore, Marianne., (Box 4)
  With blurred botanical background, looking left, her left hand gripping her right wrist.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,629.
  Number on photograph: 150-25; 195-25; Kodak Safety 47.
- Moore, Marianne., (Box 4)
  Seated, with gray background, chin slightly lowered.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,630.
  Number on photograph: 150-20; 195-20; Kodak Safety 47.
- Moore, Marianne., (Box 4)
  Seated on back of chair, with her right hand in her lap.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,631.
  Number on photograph: 150-1; 195-1.
- Moore, Marianne., (Box 4)
  Standing by hedge with gloves clasped in her right hand.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,632.
  Number on photograph: 150-4; 195-4.
- Moore, Marianne., (Box 4)
  Seated, looking forward with unbuttoned cape and gloves clasped in her right hand.
  HTC No.: HTC 22,662.
- Moore, Marianne., (Box 4)
  Standing against wall, holding gloves, looking up right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,820.
  Number on photograph: 195-10.
- Moore, Marianne., (Box 4)
  Seated, looking forward, wearing unbuttoned cape, holding glove in her left hand.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,821.
- Moore, Marianne., (Box 4)
  Seated in armchair, leaning against right arm of chair, her left hand at her collar and her right hand holding a glove.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,822.
  Number on photograph: 195-13.
- Moore, Marianne., (Box 4)
  Seated in armchair, leaning against right arm of chair, her left hand at her neck and her right hand holding a glove.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,823.
  Number on photograph: 195-24.
- Moore, Marianne., (Box 4)
  Standing against wall, holding gloves, looking up left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,824.
  Number on photograph: 195-11.
- Moore, Marianne., (Box 4)
  Seated against blank background, looking forward and slightly left, her light dress visible under dark jacket, wearing hat decorated with semicircular bows, holding white gloves, a number of pencilled markings on back of photo.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,825.
- Moore, Marianne., (Box 4)
  Standing, leaning against drafting table beside half-open window.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,826.
  Number on photograph: 195-18.
- Moorehaus, Marion., (Box 4)
  In office, seated with her left elbow on desk, looking left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,741.
- Moylan, Mary Ellen., (Box 4)
  Standing in fifth position in front of white cutout background, wearing ballet costume, looking up.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,827.
  Number on photograph: 23A2.
- Moylan, Mary Ellen., (Box 4)
  Dancer, in ballet costume, seated and looking down, her arms draped over her left leg towards the bottom right of photo.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,828.
- Newberry, John S.., (Box 4)
  HTC No.: HTC 20,633.
  Number on photograph: 157-16.
- Newberry, John S.., (Box 4)
  Seated, facing left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,634.
  Number on photograph: 157-17.
- O'Connell, Dick., (Box 4)
  By pool, in white swim trunks, looking down at stone floor.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,829.
- Ossorio, Alfonso., (Box 4)
  Seated in canvas chair under tent-like canopy of wrinkled cloth, an empty canvas chair at left, a man (visible from shoulders down) walking out of the picture at right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,830.
- Ossorio, Alfonso, 1937., (Box 4)
  In studio setup with wrinkled paper hanging overhead, holding a piece of the same material to his chest to cover his entire body except for arms and head.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,892.
- Paley, Nathalie (Princess)., (Box 4)
  Seated, in black dress, looking left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,966.
  Number on photograph: G6 (?).
- Parker, Dorothy., (Box 4)
  Seated, arms crossed across chest.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,635.
  Number on photograph: 890-3.
- Perelman, S.J.., (Box 4)
  Seated, leaning against wall, facing right, hands clasped around knees.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,962.
- Perlin, Bernard, 1940., (Box 4)
  Wearing dress shirt and tie, arms raised and crossed on top of head, facing front.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,920.
- Perlin, Bernard, 1945., (Box 4)
  Shown from elbows up, facing front, wearing dress shirt and tie, tie tucked into shirt.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,921.
- Perlin, Bernard, 1945., (Box 4)
  Seated on chair against blank background, facing front, hands in lap, his right foot resting on chair rung.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,922.
- Perlin, Bernie., (Box 4)
  Standing, thumb hooked in waistband.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,636.
  Number on photograph: 204-0.
- Platt, Joseph B.., (Box 4)
  Matted photo; Platt standing with his knee on table, to the left of a curtain, a door slightly ajar behind him.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,831.
- Pomeroy, Ralph., (Box 4)
  Standing beside bed frame, floor strewn with newspapers, smiling.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,832.
  Number on photograph: No. 5.
- Pomeroy, Ralph., (Box 4)
  Seated on bed frame, floor strewn with newspapers, looking left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,833.
  Number on photograph: 334-13; No. 8.
- Porter, Katherine Anne, 1947., (Box 4)
  Sitting on couch, wearing striped skirt, holding doll's head, her right arm extended, her head turned left, eyes closed.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,894.
- Porter, Katherine Anne, 1940., (Box 4)
  With two paintings of Monroe Wheeler by Pavel Tchelitchev; wearing dark dress and looking right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,895.
- Porter, Katherine Anne, 1947., (Box 4)
  Wearing white halter top, leaning on chair back from behind, looking up right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,896.
- Porter, Katherine Anne, 1940., (Box 4)
  Wearing black ball gown, seated and leaning against wall with flower bouquet in foreground.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,897.
  Number on photograph: 1361 3.
- Porter, Katherine Anne, Exterior of Lynes's Hollywood home, 1947., (Box 4)
  Standing on balcony in white dress, looking front, smiling.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,951.
- Porter, Katherine Anne, Exterior of Lynes's Hollywood home, 1947., (Box 4)
  Sitting on steps in white dress, her right hand on her left knee, facing front, smiling.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,952.
- Porter, Katherine Anne, Exterior of Lynes's Hollywood home, 1947., (Box 4)
  Standing on steps in white dress, hands raised in front of her, looking right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,953.
- Porter, Katherine Anne, 1940., (Box 4)
  Sitting in chair in black dress, looking right, flowered wallpaper on wall behind her.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,954.
- Porter, Katherine Anne, 1940., (Box 4)
  Sitting in chair in black dress, looking right and front (at an angle), flowered wallpaper on wall behind her.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,955.
- Porter, Katherine Anne, 1950., (Box 4)
  Undersized photograph (approx. 7 7/16" by 7 7/16"); sitting in wicker chair, arms raised, looking up, smiling.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,956.
- Porter, Katherine Anne, 1950., (Box 4)
  Undersized photograph (approx. 7 3/4" by 7 10/16"); outside, looking left at house under renovation, arms behind back.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,957.
- Porter, Katherine Anne; Lynes, George Platt, Exterior of Lynes's Hollywood home, 1947., (Box 4)
  Porter standing on balcony in white dress, looking left; Lynes standing at ground level, leaning against wall with back to camera, looking up at Porter, arms crossed above head.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,946.
- Porter, Katherine Anne; Lynes, George Platt, Exterior of Lynes's Hollywood home, 1947., (Box 4)
  Porter standing on balcony in white dress, looking front, smiling; Lynes standing at ground level, facing camera, holding leaf.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,947.
- Porter, Katherine Anne; Lynes, George Platt, Exterior of Lynes's Hollywood home, 1947., (Box 4)
  Porter standing on balcony in white dress, looking front; Lynes kneeling at ground level, looking front.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,948.
- Porter, Katherine Anne; Lynes, George Platt, Exterior of Lynes's Hollywood home, 1947., (Box 4)
  Porter standing on balcony in white dress, looking left; Lynes kneeling at ground level, looking left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,949.
- Porter, Katherine Anne; Lynes, George Platt, Exterior of Lynes's Hollywood home, 1947., (Box 4)
  Porter standing on balcony in white dress, looking left; Lynes standing at ground level, leaning against wall with back to camera, looking down, arms above head.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,950.
- Porter, Paul., (Box 4)
  Looking out window frame, arms crossed, looking down.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,834.
- Porter, Paul., (Box 4)
  Looking out window frame, his right arm on his left arm and his left arm on the window frame, looking left and slightly down.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,835.
- Prokosch, Frederick., (Box 4)
  Wearing dress pants, dress shirt, and tie; sitting on ground leaning against riser, looking down and left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,836.
- Prokosch, Frederick., (Box 4)
  Wearing V-neck sweater, seated with hands in pockets, looking up left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,837.
- Prokosch, Frederick., (Box 4)
  Wearing V-neck sweater, seated with his left leg propped up and his left elbow resting on left knee, holding his right index finger in his left hand, looking right.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,838.
  Number on photograph: 18.
- Prokosch, Frederick, 1937., (Box 4)
  Reclining on platform, weight supported by his left arm, wearing all white, looking at camera.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,907.
  Number on photograph: 1 10.
- Prokosch, Frederick, 1937., (Box 4)
  Reclining on platform, weight supported by his left arm, shirtless, looking left.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,913.
- Richter, Ray., (Box 5)
  Head shot, lying on blank white backdrop, shirtless, looking down, face contained in bottom half of photograph.
  HTC No.: HTC 20,839.
- Richter, Ray., (Box 5)